Guide to the St. Mark's Dance Company and Studio records, 1950-1998 MS2004
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administrative records, 1950-1992; MS2004 Series 1
  - Public Relations: Class Schedules, St. Mark's Dance Studio and Craighill Studio, 1970-1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Public Relations: Performance Schedules and Repertoires, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company and Arlington Dance Theatre, 1970-1975 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Public Relations: Announcements and Advertisements, St. Mark's Dance Company and Studio, 1970-1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Public Relations: Booking Information, Arlington Dance Theatre, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Public Relations: Clippings, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Public Relations: Fliers and Brochures, Arlington Dance Theatre, 1971 ca. --1975 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Public Relations: General Information, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Public Relations: Season Information, St. Mark's Dance Studio and Craighill Studio, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Public Relations: Press Releases, St. Mark's Dance Company and Studio, 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Public Relations: Articles, St. Mark's Dance Company and Studio, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Public Relations: Performance Schedules and Repertoires, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1976-1987 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Public Relations: Class Schedules, St. Mark's Dance Studio, 1976-1989 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Public Relations: Season Information, St. Mark's Dance Studio, 1976-1989 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Public Relations: Brochures, St. Mark's Dance Company and Studio and Craighill Studio, 1976 ca. --1993 ca. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Public Relations: Clippings, St. Mark's Dance Company and Studio, 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Public Relations: Mission Statement, St. Mark's Dance Studio and Junior and Senior Companies, 1978 ca. (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Public Relations: Booking Kit, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Public Relations: Reviews, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Public Relations: Booking Kits, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Public Relations: Booking Kit, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1981 ca. (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Public Relations: Press Releases, St. Mark's Dance Company and Studio, 1981 ca. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Public Relations: Fliers, St. Mark's Dance Company and Studio, 1981-1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Public Relations: Booking Kit, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Public Relations: Announcements and Advertisements, St. Mark's Dance Company and Studio, 1982-1987 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Public Relations: Article, St. Mark's Dance Company and Studio, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Public Relations: List of Compositions, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Public Relations: Announcements and Advertisements, St. Mark's Dance Company and Studio, n.d., undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Public Relations: Articles/Essays by Mary Craighill, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Public Relations: Clippings, St. Mark's Church, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Performances, programs, and special events files, 1951-1994; MS2004 Series 2
  This series consists of approximately nine boxes. This series consists of materials chronologically arranged by performance, program, or special event. These materials include programs, photographs, correspondence, schedules, negatives, slides clippings, notes, teaching notes, choreography notes, notebooks, one large book, one volume of bound papers, speeches, lectures, lists, and lyrics, dating from 1951 to 1994.
  - Dance Theatre, 1951-1953 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - School for Young Dancers, 1951-1953 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Bear Party, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Arlington County, 1952-1955 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Dance Department of the YWCA, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - The Arts Club of Washington, 1953-1957 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Modern Dance Council of Washington DC, Inc., 1953-1959 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Creative Arts Workshops, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Dance Education and the Child, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - The 18th-Century Theatrical Dance, 1955 May (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - The 18th-Century Theatrical Dance, 1955 May (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - The 18th-Century Theatrical Dance, 1955 May (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Gallaudet College's Chapel Service, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Washington Cathedral Pageant, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Washington Cathedral Pageant, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Children's International Friendship Party, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - The Montgomery Jewish Community, 1956 ca. --1957 ca. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Revels, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Mary Craighill Studio's Year-End Recitals, 1957-1966 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Washington Contemporary Dance Group, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Washington Contemporary Dance Group Concert, 1960 ca. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Washington Contemporary Dance Foundation, Inc.'s Joint Dance Concert at Roosevelt Auditorium, May, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Chancel Drama Cycle, Chancel Dance Group, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Chancel Drama Cycle, Chancel Dance Group, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Mary Craighill and Company's Lenten Dance Recital, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Materials of Dance as a Creative Art Activity, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Mary Craighill and Company, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Mary Craighill and Company, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Workshops, 1960 ca. --1965 ca. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Mary Craighill and Company, Lenten Drama Cycle, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Mary Craighill and Company, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Washington Ballet Guild "World of Dance" Lecture Series, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - St. Mark's Chancel Dance Group, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - St. Mark's Chancel Dance Group, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Tea Dance, October, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Christmastime Performances at St. Mark's Church, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Composition, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Worship Through the Arts Weekend, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Hood Conference, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Lost in the Stars, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Chancel Drama Cycle, St. Mark's Chancel Dance Group, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Lectures and Workshops on Modern Dance, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Rejoice, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Demonstration at St. Augustine's Church, 1966 March (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Stages of Man, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Folk Masses at St. Stephen's Church, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Gospel Song, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - St. Mark's Chancel Dance Group Season Repertoire, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - St. Mark's Dance Company's SUNY-Delhi Performance, December, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Studios' Year-End Recitals, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Liturgical Symphony, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Rejoice, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Dance in the Schools, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Patrick Hayes Broadcast, 1968 ca. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - The Arts and the Inner City Conference, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Stages of Man, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Studios' Year-End Recitals, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Lent Performance at St. Mark's Church, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Studios' Year-End Recitals, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Teacher Workshops, DC Public Schools, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Sources of Dance in the U.S.A., Sears-Roebuck, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - St. Mark's Junior Company, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - St. Mark's Junior Company, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Craighill Studio Year-End Recital, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Gum Springs Workshops, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Gum Springs Workshops, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - St. Mark's Church Chapel Service Performances, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Arlington County Pilot Project, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Academic Workshops, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Arlington-St. Mark's Senior and Junior Companies, 1971-1975 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Studios' Year-End Recitals, 1971-1979 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Easter Worship Service, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Teacher Training Workshop, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Academic Workshops, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Arlington Elementary Schools Humanities Project, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Arlington Elementary Schools Humanities Project, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Humanities Project, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Humanities Project, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Revels, 1973-1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Children's Package, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Arlington Dance Theatre, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - St. Mark's Junior Company, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Lunch Theatre, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Mar Salle Convalescent Center, St. Mark's Junior Company, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Sacred Dance Guild Institute, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Sacred Dance Guild Institute, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Sacred Dance Guild Institute, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - City Celebration, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - St. Mark's Dance Company, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Lunch Theatre, 1975-1981 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - International Children's Festival at Wolf Trap, 1975-1982 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Christmas Performance, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Fernwood House, St. Mark's Junior Company, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Lunch Theatre, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Choreographer's Night, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Christ Church Lenten Dinner Program, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Christmas Performance, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Epiphany Sunday at St. Mark's, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Lunch Theatre, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Repertoire of Religious Dance, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Showcase Performance, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Summerdance, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - St. Mark's Dance Company Concert Repertoires, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Christmas Performance, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Lunch Theatre, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Lunch Theatre, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Lunch Theatre, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - WRC-TV, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Lycoming College, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Peter and the Wolf & Christmas Carol, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - St. Mark's Dance Company Current Active Performing Repertoire, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Lunch Theatre, 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Preschool, 1979 ca. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Cherry Tree Carol, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Christmas Performance, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Crossroads, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Goodwin House, St. Mark's Junior Company, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - International Seminar on the Bible in Dance, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - International Seminar on the Bible in Dance, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - International Seminar on the Bible in Dance, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - International Seminar on the Bible in Dance papers Presented at the Seminar, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Library for the Arts District of Columbia Public Library Performance, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Lunch Theatre, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Lunch Theatre, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - St. Mark's Dance Company Current Active Performing Repertoire, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Lunch Theatre, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Lunch Theatre, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Metropolitan Dance Association Awards Reception, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Salome at St. Mark's Church, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - St. Mark's Dance Company Current Active Performing Repertoire, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - St. Mark's Dance Studio Year-End Recitals, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Lunch Theatre, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Revels, 1980-1990 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Revels, 1980-1990 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Revels, 1980-1990 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Prince George's Publick Playhouse, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Prince George's Publick Playhouse, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Prince George's Publick Playhouse, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Prince George's Publick Playhouse, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - St. Mark's Episcopal Church, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Gala Concert-Dinner-Disco, 1981 May (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - AV Workshop, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Capitol Children's Museum, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Lent, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - St. Mark's Dance Company at Utopia Theatre, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - St. Mark's Junior Company, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Sir Gawain and the Green Knight, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - A Concert for Spring, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Glen Echo Park, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Sir Gawain and the Green Knight, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - The Story of a Soldier, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - St. Mark's Dance Studio Year-End Recitals, 1982-1994 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Dance Fest '83, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Grace Cathedral, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - St. Mark's Dance Company Annual Workshops, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Pacific School of Religion: Stretching Sacred Dance, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Calvary Church Service, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - International Dance Week, Dance Fest, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Repertory Dance Theatre of Chicago, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - St. Mark's Dance Company 25th Anniversary Concert, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Documentary/Video on Liturgical/Sacred Dance, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Library of Congress Lecture, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Logos Conference, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Creative Workshop, St. Mark's Junior Company, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Dmitrieff Studios Silver Jubilee Performance, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Festival of the Arts Six, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Festival Workshop of Drama and Dance, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Materials of Composition, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Rock Springs Lecture, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous files, 1956-1998; MS2004 Series 3; 0.5 Linear feet
  This series consists of materials dating from 1956 to 1998. These miscellaneous files include newsletters, correspondence, and minutes of other organizations, zoning records, legal documents, and several unidentified documents. The series is arranged chronologically to the most possible extent. Many articles have no date and are unidentifiable. Throughout the series, for preservation and ease of use, clippings have been photocopied and mylar sleeves protect aging onion skin paper.
  - Modern Dance Council of Washington DC, Inc., Modern Dance In Washington, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Modern Dance Council of Washington DC, Inc., Modern Dance In Washington, 1958-1965 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Kennedy Center/Washington Arts Council, 1961-1970 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Kennedy Center/Washington Arts Council, 1961-1970 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Kennedy Center/Washington Arts Council, 1961-1970 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - St. Mark's Dance Studio Zoning, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - St. Mark's Dance Studio Zoning, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - ASCAP, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Recommendations to Teachers and Supervisors, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Religious Dance Material, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Annual reports, 1989-1997; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Budgeting, 1974; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Budgeting and information, 1965-1968; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Chancel Dance Group / St. Mark's Dance company information, Circa 1966; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Choreography, Circa 1990; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Class schedules and registration information, 1996; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Community service, 1985; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1976; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1998; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Finance information, 1966-1969; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Finance information, 1992, 1998; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Grant information and applications, 1966; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - International performance materials, 1989-1995; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Invitations and announcements, Undated; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Junior Company, 1994-1997; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Liturgical dance conferences, 1990; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Lunch Theater programs, 1976; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Memorandums, 1974; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Modern Dance Council information, 1966; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Newsletters, 1967-1991; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Organizational meetings, 1986; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Performance flyers and programs, 1967-1995; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Proprietary school license material, 1972-1974; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Publications, 1978, 1986; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Religious ceremonies, 1963-1969; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Reviews, articles, and advertisements, 1967; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Reviews, articles, and advertisements, 1980; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Season, 1997-1998; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - St. Mark's dance fund, 1984; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Studio brochures, Undated; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Studio correspondence and information, 1966-1968; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Tax information, 1974; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Zoning regulations, 1974; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Non-print media, 1950-1988; MS2004 Series 4
  Most photographs, negatives and slides include scenes from performances and illustrate details of dance, scenery, costume or location. The materials, photographs and a few notes about them, in the Photographs sub-series constitute the bulk of this series and date from ca. 1950 to 1987. The photographs are arranged chronologically by performance, program, or special event. The majority are black and white photographs of all sizes but there are many small color photographs as well. The Slides sub-series, chronologically arranged by performance, program, or special event, dates from ca. 1966 to 1977. There are both color and black and white slides. The Negatives sub-series, chronologically arranged by performance, program, or special event, dates from the 1950's to 1979. There are both color and black and white negatives. The Audiotapes sub-series consists of reel-to-reel audiotapes and two audio cassette tapes. These include music from performances and lectures. These are arranged chronologically as far as possible, but most of the items are undated. The Videotapes sub-series consists of a videocassette tape, reel-to-reel video tapes, and film. The video cassettes include footage from lectures, newsreals and conferences. These materials are arranged chronologically by performance, program, or special event and date from 1950o 1988.
  - Photographs: Gospel Song, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1966 ca. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Gospel Song, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1966 ca. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Gospel Song, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1966 ca. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: Gospel Song, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1966 ca. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: Stages of Man, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1966 ca. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: Stages of Man, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1966 ca. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Stages of Man, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1966 ca. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Stages of Man, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1966 ca. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Stages of Man, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1966 ca. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: I Know That My Redeemer Liveth, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1967 ca. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: Rejoice, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1967 ca. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Nottingham Publicity, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Bizet, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: Liturgical Symphony, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1968 ca. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: Liturgical Symphony, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1968 ca. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: Liturgical Symphony, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1968 ca. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Liturgical Symphony, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1968 ca. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Liturgical Symphony, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1968 ca. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: St. Mark's Junior Company, 1968 ca. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: Annual Pictures, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: St. Mark's Dance Company, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: Blue Memory, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1969 February (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: Gum Springs Workshop, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Photographs: Pilot Project, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Photographs: Pilot Project, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Photographs: Recital, Murray Mitchell, St. Mark's Dance Studio, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Workshops, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1972 ca. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: Jo Tartt, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1972 ca. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: Eugene Onegin, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Bear Tracks, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Heart of Gold, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Peter and the Wolf, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: Sylvie, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: Insect Comedy, St. Mark's Junior Company, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: Cruel Sea, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: Michele, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Photographs: Pas de Trois, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Photographs: Peter and the Wolf, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Peter and the Wolf, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Sam Maddy, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: Suite from the Magnificat, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: Where the Wild Things Are, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: Julie Craighill and Mary Craighill, Scarlatti Suite, Arlington-St. Mark's Junior Company, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Scarlatti Suite, Arlington-St. Mark's Dance Company, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Arlington Dance Theatre, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Arlington-St. Mark's Junior Company, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: St. Mark's Dance Studio, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: Wolf Trap, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1975 ca. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: Wolf Trap, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1975 ca. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: Wolf Trap, St. Mark's Dance Company, 1975 ca. (Box 23, Folder 13)